--==CMCT团队 荣誉出品==--
影片压制: 南山石  字幕调校: 清风
www.
招募Q号:76846146
--==CMCT团队 荣誉出品==--
影片压制: 南山石  字幕调校: 清风
www.H
招募Q号:76846146
--==CMCT团队 荣誉出品==--
影片压制: 南山石  字幕调校: 清风
www.HD
招募Q号:76846146
--==CMCT团队 荣誉出品==--
影片压制: 南山石  字幕调校: 清风
www.HDc
招募Q号:76846146
--==CMCT团队 荣誉出品==--
影片压制: 南山石  字幕调校: 清风
www.HDcm
招募Q号:76846146
--==CMCT团队 荣誉出品==--
影片压制: 南山石  字幕调校: 清风
www.HDcmc
招募Q号:76846146
--==CMCT团队 荣誉出品==--
影片压制: 南山石  字幕调校: 清风
www.HDcmct
招募Q号:76846146
--==CMCT团队 荣誉出品==--
影片压制: 南山石  字幕调校: 清风
www.HDcmct.
招募Q号:76846146
--==CMCT团队 荣誉出品==--
影片压制: 南山石  字幕调校: 清风
www.HDcmct.c
招募Q号:76846146
--==CMCT团队 荣誉出品==--
影片压制: 南山石  字幕调校: 清风
www.HDcmct.co
招募Q号:76846146
--==CMCT团队 荣誉出品==--
影片压制: 南山石  字幕调校: 清风
www.HDcmct.com
招募Q号:76846146
片名：性.谎言.录影带
垃圾
Garbage.
我这礼拜想的只有垃圾
All I've been thinking about all weekis garbage.
我无法不去想
I can't stop thinking about it.
垃圾的什么问题呢？
What kind of thoughts about garbage?
我担心到底会怎么样
I just... I've gotten real concerned over
what's gonna happen with all the garbage.
有那么多垃圾
I mean, we've got so much of it.
我们的垃圾太多了
You know? I mean, we have to run out
最後我们一定会没地方放的
of places to put this stuff eventually.
上回...
The last time...
我开始有这种感觉
I started feelin' this wayis when that barge was stranded
是因为那　船搁浅绕著岛转  没有人认
and, you know, it was goin' around
the island and nobody would claim it.
你记得那个新闻吧？我记得
- Do you remember that?
- Yes, I remember.
你知道为什么使你担心这个吗
Do you have any idea
what may have triggered this concern?
好
Yeah.
你知道，那个晚上
You see, the other night
John was taking out the garbage,
约翰把垃圾拿出去倒的时候 东西一直从垃圾桶掉出来
and he kept spilling things out of the container,
我就开始想像到 有个垃圾桶会生出垃圾来
and that made me I started imagining, like,
a garbage can that produces garbage.
而且一直不停
And it doesn't stop, it keeps producinggarbage.
不断地生出垃圾来
And it keeps overflowing.
这种事你有什么办法制止？
And, you know, what would you do
to try to stop something like that?
安，你有没看出什么模式？
- Ann, do you see any pattern here?
- What do you mean?
你这话是什么意思？
Well, last week we were talking about
上礼拜谈的是你担心空难
your obsession with
the families of airline fatalities.
现在你又再担心垃圾问题
Now we're talking about your
concern over the garbage problem.
对，那又如何？
Yeah... So?
想想看，你最忧心的
Well, if you think about it, I think
you'll see the object of your obsession
总是你没办法控制的坏事
is invariably something negative
which you have no control over.
对
Yeah
可是有多少人会去困扰 事情有多棒有多开心的呢？
but how many people do  you thinkrun around
obsessing overhow great and how happy things are?
说不定也有，不过我想 这种人就不用心理治疗了
You know, I mean, maybe they do,
but I don't think they're in therapy.
而且开心也没什么了不起
Anyway... bein' happy isn't all that great.
上回我真正很开心的时候
I mean, the last time
I was really happy, I got so fat.
我好胖，至少重了25磅
I must've put on 25 pounds.
当时我以为约翰会吓成中风
I thought John was gonna have a stroke.
你担心什么？
- So, what are you worried about?
- What am I looking at here?
我看到的是什么？弄错了吧？
那要看你的观点如何了
- Is this a mistake?
- Depends on your point of view.
我觉得没错
I don't think so. In fact,
我告诉你一个秘密
I'm gonna tell you a little secret.
只要你戴了结婚戒指
As soon as you get a ring on your finger,
you start getting spectacular attention
异性就会特别注意你
- from the opposite gender.
- That's bullshit!
胡说八道
真希望我每场能看足球大赛
Seriously. I wish I had
Super Bowl seats for every time
总有漂亮小姐主动送上门
some filly had come up and talked to me
without the slightest provocation.
会受非难，但太棒了
- It's just marvellous.
- That happened before you got married.
那是你结婚以前的事 结婚以前从来就没碰到过
No, no, no.It never happened before I got married.
要是早知道的话
If I'd known, I'd have bought a ring
我十八岁就去买个戒指
when I was 18 and saved myself
可以省下好多时间和金钱
Yeah, right!
...a lot of time and money.
真希望早有人告诉我这个秘密
No, I wish somebody'd clued me in.
我告诉你
I'm tellin' you.
这太怪异了
It's too weird.
妈的，我得动身了
Oh, shit, I gotta be someplace.
礼拜四打回力球？
So, racquetball Thursday, right?
七点半？好，改天见，拜拜
- How about 7.30?- Yeah, fine. See you later. Bye.- Bye-bye.
珍尼...把柯南的约会改在礼拜五下午一点半好的
- Yes, sir?- Janet.Reschedule Kirkland for, uh, Friday, 1:30.
- Yes, sir.- All right.
你这些想法都没让约翰知道吧
Are you still
keeping these thoughts from John?
是的
Yeah.
是怕他的反应？怕他笑你傻？
Are you afraid of his finding you silly
at thinking these things?
不是，不是因为这些
No, it's not that. It's just...
只是我正在跟他生气，为什么？
- I'm really angry at him right now.
- Why?
他请这个大学同学到家里来住
He invited this college friend of his to、stay at our house
事先都没问过我
and didn't even ask me.
我当然会答应的，可是...
I'm gonna say yes, of course, but...
先问过我不是更好吗？
you know, it just would've
been nice to have been asked.
这种事你火什么呢？
What upsets you about that?
我气的是我没资格生气
I guess it makes me angry
because I can't justify bein' angry.
房子是他的贷款的钱是他在付，对
It's his house. He pays the mortgage.
可是当初是他叫你不要上班的
你要做家事
Yes, but he asked you to quit your job,
and you do have housework.
嗯，我要做家事一点不错
Yeah. I have housework. That's true.
除了这位不速之客的事
This unexpected guest notwithstanding,
你和约翰之间如何？
how are things with John?
不错，不错
Oh, they're fine.
只是我有点不想让他碰我
Except for I'm going through this thing
where I don't want him to touch me, but...
你什么时候开始有这种感觉的
When did you begin having this feeling?
上礼拜，我不知道，我只是.
Well... last week.
我突然有这种奇怪的感觉
I don't know, I just... I got this
really strange feelin', and... ugh...
就是不想让他碰我
just didn't want him to touch me.
在那之前，你和约翰之间
Prior to this feeling, were you
夫妻性生活还好吧？
comfortable with contact with John?
啊，很好，当然，很好
Oh, yeah. Sure. Yeah.
只不过...
Except for... well...
我向来不怎么在乎那档事
I've never really been that much into sex.
我是说，也喜欢啦，不过...
I mean, I like it and everything, but...
你知道，我只是......
You know, I just don't think
不觉得有什么了不得的
it's such a big deal, and...
你知道，没有也无所谓，不过...
I wouldn't miss it, you know, kinda thing.
最近我也奇怪，怎么少下来了
But lately I've just... been kinda curious
about how things have slacked off.
也许他感觉到你，不想让他碰你
Perhaps he senses
your hesitance at being touched.
可是怪的就在这里
But that's the weird thing,
because he started not touching me
我还没这种感觉之前
他就不碰我了
before I started feelin' like that.
我相信他希望我偶尔会主动  我也可以主动啦，只不过...
I mean, I'm sure he probably wishes
that I would initiate things once in a while,
我从来没想要过
and I would, except for it just never occurs to me, and...
偶而想到，又总是一个人的时候
well, the few times
I have felt like it I was by myself.
那有没有怎么样呢？
Did you do anything?
你这话是什么意思？
What do you mean?
有没有自慰？
Did you masturbate?
天啦，没有
God, no.
No. Mm-mm.
看你的反应，好像从没自慰过
I take it from your response
that you never masturbate.
我试过一次
Well... I tried once.
只觉得这种事好笨
It just seems so stupid!
我不知道，只觉得那样好笨
I don't know! It just seemed like
a dumb thing to do, and...
然後我又开始担心
God, and then I started worrying that my
已经去世的爷爷会不会在看我
dead grandfather was watching me, and...
那种事好像很笨
It seemed so stupid, especially when you
尤其是还不知道垃圾怎么处理
don't know what to do with the garbage.
原来你是最近才试的？
Oh, so it was recently
when you tried this?
也算是最近吧
Oh, well, it was kind of recently,
不过也不太近啦
but not... real recently.
我只是不想在家里住个客人
I am just not up to
havin' a guest in the house.
我得回办公室，非回去不可了
I gotta go. I gotta go to the office.
I gotta get back to the office.
今天只有一回合啊？
I only get one today?
哎，真过隐
Gee, how exciting.
我已经溜了一个会非回去不可
I already skipped one meeting.I gotta get back.
我说，约翰...你要走就走
Look, John, if you wanna leave, leave.
我又不是单为跟你碰头才活着  别把自己捧得太高
My life doesn't revolve around these
little get-togethers. Don't flatter yourself.
我不认为你必须温和地对我 然後再告诉我你实在的感觉
Don't feel like you gotta treat me with
kid gloves. Tell me how you really feel.
我有个朋友要来
Listen, I got a friend comin' into town,
那个朋友已经多年不见了
an old friend I haven't seen in years.
我觉得他好像有点失落
From what I can tell,
I think he's a little lost.
恐怕我得花点时间陪他
I think I may have
to spend a little time with him.
是说我们之间得冷一阵子罗？
Mm-hm.
Meaning we'll have to cool it for a while?
- Yeah.
我希望你别再到酒吧打工了
I wish you'd quit
that bartending job of yours.
为什么？
Why?
想到那些男人追你，我就难过
I hate the thought
of all those guys hittin' on you.
我应付得了
I can handle it.
那当然
I'm sure.
再说，薪水不错
有些男人长得也挺帅的
Besides, the money is good,
and some of the guys are cute.
你没资格吃醋
And you are in no position to be jealous.
谁说我吃醋来著？
Who said I was jealous?
我说
I did.
你知道...
You know
我想到你家和你上床
I'd like to do it at your house sometime.
想到能和你在我姐姐床上做爱  就叫我兴奋得要死
I must admit, the idea of doin' it in my
sister's bed gives me a perverse thrill.
我希望我可以堂而皇之的  跟每个人说安在床上差劲透了
I wish I could just come right out
and tell everyone Ann's a lousy lay.
那位既美丽又受欢迎的安小姐
The beautiful, the popular
Ann Bishop Millaney.
那样太冒险了
我来散布这样的谣言，好不好？
- Could be risky.
- How about I just start a rumour, then?
不是，我是说在我家做爱
怕被逮到吗？对
- No, no, I mean doin' it at my house.
- Afraid of gettin' caught?
你该怕才对
Yeah!
You should be.
我能不能见见你的那个朋友？
- Can I meet this friend of yours?
- Who, Graham?
葛伦？多年前我们很亲近
I gotta tell you, we were very close
many years ago, but I...
可是现在我们大不相同了
I think we're very different now.
安？我叫葛伦.达顿
- Yes?
- Ann? Uh, my name is Graham Dalton.
能不能借个洗手间用一下？
- Oh! Yeah, sure.
- May I use your bathroom?
请进
Uh-huh. Come on in.
在那里？後面左边，对不起
- Where is it?
- Oh, back there to the left. I'm sorry.
你喜不喜欢草莓？
Do you like strawberries?
I brought you some.
谢谢你，你太客气了
Thank you. That's real sweet.
接约翰梅南尼，我是他太太
Hi. Um, John Millaney, please.
This is his wife.
没关系，谢谢你
That's all right. Thank you.
你可真快，假警报
Well.
- That was quick.
- False alarm.
请坐
Have a seat.
抱歉，我们家里不让人抽烟的
I'm sorry, we don't let people
smoke in the house.
如果你想抽烟可以到外面
- But if you'd like to, we could go outside.
不用了，我可以等一下再抽
- Oh, no, no, no, no, no. No, no.I can wait. I'm...
还有别的行李吗？有
- Do you have any other things?
- Yes.
你是说要拿进来的？不用了
Oh, you mean to bring in? No.
我还有些别的东西
I do have some other things, but I don't...
不过在这里只用得到这个
This is all I need to stay here.
你有没有上过电视？
Have you ever been on television?
上电视？没有，为什么问？
Television? No, no.
Why?
我只是好奇而巳
I was just curious.
葛伦
Graham.
这个名字很少见
That's an unusual name.
真的，我妈对英国特别感兴趣
Yeah. Yeah, l, uh... I guess it is.My mother is a complete Anglophile.
凡是英国的东西都让她兴奋
Anything Britishmakes her drool like a baby.
我想这名字是她从电影听来的
So she, you know, I think she heard the name in a movie or something.
她一天到晚看公共电视
She's a prisoner of public television now.
你觉得婚姻生活好不好？
How do you like being married?
蛮好的
I like it just fine.
你喜欢那些部份？
What about it do you like? I...
我不是想找麻烦  没关系
- I don't mean to be critical. I'm curious.
- No, no, no, no. That's OK. Uh...
你知道所谓安全感之类的老调
Well... you know the cliche about the security of it?
还真有点道理
Well, that's true.
而且这栋房子是我们自己的
And, um, we own this house.
很好的房子
It's a nice house. And...
约翰在事务所刚升成合夥人
John was just made junior partner,
我真的觉得很棒
and I really like that.
我喜欢他不只是兼差什么的
You know, I like the fact that he's just not,
you know, freelance or whatever.
你有多久没见到约翰了？
So, how long has it been since you've seen John?
九年
- Nine years.- Nine years?
没想到他让我在找到房子之前
Yeah. I was surprised he invited me
先住在这里
to stay here until I found a place.
你不是跟他很熟吗？
- Didn't you know him very well?
我跟他很熟
- Oh, no, I knew him very well.
约翰和我以前很相像的
John and I were very much alike.
真的吗？
Really?
实在叫人难以相信
That's kinda hard to believe.
现在你们看来大不相同呢！
I mean, you just seem so different now.
我想现在我们也是大不相同了
Yeah. Well, I would imagine
we are pretty different now.
我终於还是要用洗手间了，好的
- I'm ready to use the bathroom, finally.
- OK.
葛伦，我告诉你今天看到你我差点去叫警察
Graham. I gotta tell you, I almost
called the cops when I saw you today.
我觉得简直不可能就是每周
I thought to myself
"This couldn't possibly be the same guy
在学校为女选手作私人服务的人
that once held private services in
the back of the chapel on a weekly basis".
你真干过那种事？
- You did that?
每个人都有过去的嘛
Everybody has a past. That's mine, so...
你怎么会穿成这样？
So, what's with the get-up?
有人死了还是怎么著？约翰
- Somebody die, or...?
- John!
抱歉，不，没有
- I'm sorry. Did...? I'm sorry.- No, no, no.Nobody died.
你想老同学对你的黑衣怎么想
- So...- I mean...what do you think the Greeks'd think of this rather sombre attire?
我不知道
I don't know.
菜真好
Dinner was very good.
不错
Yeah, it wasn't bad, honey.
通常安用起盐来都在临界点
Usually Ann achieves a kinda critical
mass with the salt, but, uh, tonight was...
我总跟她讲要加盐可以再加 可是放多了就拿不掉了
I always tell her, you can always add more, but you can't take it away.
对，你的确说过这话
Yeah, you say that, don't you?
你有家人也住城里吗？
- So, do you have family here?
- Mm.
我妈，我爸，还有我姐妹
Mother, father, my sister.
姐姐还是妹妹？
Sister older or younger?
妹妹
- Younger.
你们很亲近吗？
Are you close?
对不起，又在打听了，抱歉
I'm sorry. I'm... I'm prying again. I'm sorry.
你先前已经盘问过她？
Were you prying before?
盘问过你们的婚姻生活
I was grilling Ann about your marriage.
经过如何？很好
- How'd it go?
- Well, I... Very well. Uh...
我刚问到你妹妹的事
So, I was asking about your sister.
我们处得不错，只不过...
Yeah. Well...We get along all right, it's just that, uh...
我想她是个很外向的人
Well, I think she's an extrovert.
我觉得她蛮粗的
I just think she's loud.
她也许不同意我的说法
She probably wouldn't agree.
她绝对不会同意的
No, I mean, definitely wouldn't agree.
你会不会去看看伊莉莎白
So, listen, are you gonna see Elizabeth while you're here?
我不知道
Uh... I don't know.
伊莉莎白是谁？
- Who's Elizabeth?
葛伦以前追过的女孩子
A girl Graham dated in school.Well after the chapel episodes.
据我所知她还住在这里
She still lives here,to the best of my knowledge.
葛伦和我谈到租房子的事
So Graham and Iwere talking about apartments,
我告诉他有很多可爱的小公寓
and I told him that they've got lovely little apartments in the Garden District.
在花园区，有车库的很不错 花园区治安不好
And they got nice garage apartments...There's critical crime in that district.
乱讲，才没有呢！
- Oh, John, come on, that is not true.- No. There are...
我不知道你要找怎样的地方
I don't know what kind of place you're lookin' for.
但别处有不少好的小公寓 对不起，不
There's plenty of apartments in any one place. I'm sorry?
像现在，我有一把钥匙 全部家当都在那部汽车里
No, I just... Right now I have one key,you know, everything I own is in the car.
我喜欢这样，要是弄间公寓
I like that.If I get an apartment, that's two keys.
就要两把钥匙，要是再找份工作  说不定要负责开门锁门
If I get a job, you know, I might have to open or close.
那钥匙会更多，买一些东西後
That's more keys.buy some stuff
又会怕被偷
I'm afraid it's gonna get ripped off
就得再多好几把钥匙
and I get more keys.
我喜欢只有一把钥匙
- I just like having the one key. It's clean.
我最讨厌丢掉钥匙
-You don't have to worry about losin'em.
租到了房子，就把车卖掉
Get rid of the car when you get the apartment. Still one key.
不行，我喜欢有部车子
I like having the car. You know?
The car's important. You gotta be mobile.
车子很重要，要来来往往的
以防万一要赶著离开
In case you have to leave someplace in a hurry?
对，或是要赶著到那里去
Yeah, or go someplace in a hurry.
我先告退了
Excuse me.
要不要帮忙？不
- Do you want some help?
- No, no, really, I'm fine.
不用了，没多少要收拾的
There's not that much to do.
你付不付所得税？
Graham, do you pay taxes?
付呀，你这话什么意思？
Yeah, I pay taxes.
Yeah, I pay taxes. What do you mean?
骗人的才不付税，我又不骗人
You don't pay taxes, you're a liar.
I'm not a liar.
骗人的是第二等最差劲的人
Liars are the second-lowest form
of human being on the planet.
什么样的人第一差劲？
- What's the first?
当律师的
- Lawyers.
对，那就是你嘛，亲爱的
Oh. That's you, honey.
你帮葛伦找房子好吗？
Annie, why don't you go with Graham
to hunt for apartments?
让他看看这里变了多少
Show him how the city's changed.
你愿意吗？太好了
- Would you mind, Graham?
- No, I'd love that.
我也喜欢，就这样办
I'd like that, too. Let's do that.
明天可以吗？
All right. How about tomorrow?
好极了
- That'd be great.
- Good.
只有一把钥匙？
One key, huh?
了不起的想法
Great idea.
辛蒂亚，我是约翰
- Yeah.
- Cynthia, John.
一小时之後到我家见面
Meet me at my house in exactly one hour.
不要脸的家伙，我会到
You are scum.
I'll be there.
你看得到，两个人住足足有馀
As you can see,
there's plenty of room for two.
不是，只有我一个人住
No, it'll just be me.
你是个学生吗？
Are you a student?
不是的
No.
浴室里装个帘子
You can hang
a shower curtain in the bath.
浴缸里放块垫子，就不会滑倒
Make sure you put somethin'
in the tub so you won't fall.
你说月租三百五？
You said about 350?
对，先付两个月算押金
Yeah. And, uh, plus
the first and the last months' rent.
你可以按月租续约吗？
- All right. Will you lease month to month?
那就不能只算三百五了
Not for 350.
四百怎么样？
How about 400?
还可以商量
I could live with that. I could live with that.
好，那就说定了
- OK. It's a deal.- All right.
可以走了吗？
- Ready?- Yeah.
约翰，我在里面
- John?- In here.
好啊，可真好看啊
Well, ain't you a picture?
怎么样？喜欢吗？
Well, do you like it?
很可爱，是给我的吗？
It's lovely. Is it for me?
嗯，是送你的
Yeah, it's for you.
这也是我的吗？
Is that for me?
嗯，也是你的
Yeah, that's for you.
妈的，你真太棒了
You're amazing, dear.
我能不能告诉你一些私人问题
Can I tell you something personal?
随便你，我也可以吗？可以
It's up to you.Can I tell you something personal?Yeah. Yeah.
你得先说，好的
Well, you gotta go first.OK.
我觉得...
I think that, um...
大家把性估量得太高了
I think that sex is overrated.
都把那事看得过份重要
I think that people place far too much importance on it.
说女人和男人一样急切　要
And I think that stuff about women
全是一派胡言
wantin' it just as bad as men is crap.
我想女人也会想要的
可是和男人所想的理由不一样
I think they want it, I just don't think they
want it for the reason men think they do.
我都搞糊涂了
I'm getting confused.
你明白吗？明白
- Do you understand what I'm...?
- Yeah.
你知道，我记得在那里...
Yeah, I remember reading somewhere
看到说男人...
学会爱上吸引他的女人
that men learn to love
the person that they're attracted to,
而女人呢？
and that women
会越来越被所爱的人吸引
become more and more attracted to the person that they love.
天啦，这种说法...太美了
God, that's... that's beautiful.
真的太美了
That's really beautiful.
我很喜欢
I like that.
我只是引用别人写的
Oh, I'm just quoting.
你愿意谈些你私人的事吗？
So, are you gonna
tell me something personal?
你要我说，是呀
- Do you want me to?
- Yeah. Yeah, I do.
我不要你谈什么伤心旧事
I don't want it to be
something gross, about some scar.
我要听真正关於你自己的事
I want it to be something
really personal, about yourself.
All right. OK.
我是个性无能
I'm impotent.
什么？
You're what?
性无能
Impotent.
真的？
You are?
是的，我是说我不能
Yeah. I mean, like, well, I can't...
我没法勃起
I can't get an erection...
在别人面前就不行
in the presence of another person.
所以说起来，我是个性无能
So, for all practical purposes,I'm impotent.
这事让你很困扰吗？
Does that bother you?
不会
No.
会不会让你很自卑呢？
Does it make you feel self-conscious?
通常不会
Not usually.
是的，我是有点太自卑
No. Uh...
Yeah, I'm self-conscious.
不过和你的情形不一样
Not in the same way
that you are, though.
我？你认为我很自卑吗？
- Me? Me? You think I'm self-conscious?
- Well...
我一直在注意你
I been watching you.
注意你吃，注意你说话
I watch you eat,you know, I watch you speak,
我注意你的动作
watch you move
我觉得你是个会很注意到别人在看你的人
and I see somebody who is extremely aware of people looking at you.
我的心理医生...你在接受心理治疗？
- My therapist...- You're in therapy?
你没有吗？
Aren't you?
我没有
No. I... No, I'm not.
在这方面我是个可怜的失败者
I was a miserable failure in therapy.
你不相信心理治疗？
So you don't believe in therapy?
我相信对某些人有用
No, I believe in it for some people.
但我觉得很笨
I don't know, it was,you know, silly for me.
这种治疗会让我更迷惑
I was confused going in.
所以我有自己的一套理论
So I just formed my own theory
就是绝对不要接受
that you should never take advice
对你没有深刻认识的人的忠告
from someone that doesn't know you intimately.
我和我的心理医师认识很深
Well, I know my therapist intimately.
你和医生有过肌肤之亲？不
- You've had sex with your therapist?- No!
对不起，我不是这个意思
- No. No.
- Oh, no, I'm sorry. That's what I meant.
我是说有肉体关系的人
Somebody you've had sex with.
Oh.
我不懂
I'm... I don't understand.
你怎么知道？
I mean, how would you know?
我是说你怎么...我并不是一直是个性无能的人
- I mean, you know. How...?- Oh, no. I wasn't always impotent.
那，让我弄弄清楚
So, let me see. You said, um...
你是说...
you said that
我不该听那些
I should never take advice
没和我上过床的人的忠告？
对吗？
from someone that
I haven't had sex with, right?
基本上是如此
- Basically.
- Right.
我们之间没有这种关系
And, uh, we haven't had sex.
对不对？
- Right?
- No.
所以我想根据你的忠告
我不该接受你的忠告
So I guess from your own advice,
I shouldn't take your advice.
如果是我就不会，你不会
- I wouldn't.
- You wouldn't? OK.
开车小心点
- Drive safely.
- Yeah, right.
周末过得怎么样？
- How was your weekend?
还好
- It was OK.
你有没为客人的事和约翰争吵
- Did you confront John about the visitor?
客人？
- The visitor?
说要暂住你家的那个朋友
The friend of John's
that was staying at your house.
葛伦
- Graham.
不错，我是说...
Yeah. I mean... no.
没有，後来发现蛮有意思的
That actually
turned out to be interesting.
我原以为他会和约翰一样
You know, I was expecting him
to be just like John.
因为他们以前是同学
You know, cos they went
to school together and everything.
你知道，会聊些...
You know, talking about getting drunk
一起喝醉酒之类的旧事
together and secret handshakes and...
结果却发现他是个
He turned out to be
很有意思的人
really this character.
他有点艺术家的模样
He's kind of arty.
不过人很好
But OK.
他还住在你家里吗？
Is he still at your house?
没有，没有，已经搬走了
No. No. No. He's gone.
他是那里人？
So where's he from?
我不知道
I don't know.
他以前住过纽约和费城
He, uh, used to live in New York and Philadelphia.
我想他一直到处走动
I think he just kinda travels around.
这样想必很过隐
Must be nice.
他像不像约翰？
So, what's he like? Is he like John?
不像
No.
我觉得约翰现在不再喜欢他了
I don't think John likes him any more.
他说他变得奇怪
Says he thinks he's gotten kinda strange.
他怪不怪呢？
Is he? Strange, I mean?
不怪
No.
不过要是在路上碰到他
I mean, if I saw him on the street
我可能会觉得他很怪
I might think so,
在认得他跟他谈过话之後
but after talkin' to him,
我只能说他与众不同
I'd just say he's kinda unusual.
他长得怎么样？
Mm-hm. So, what's he look like?
做什么？
Why?
我想知道，好去追他？
- I just wanna know, is all.
- Why, so you can go after him?
想到那里去了
Jesus, Ann, get a life.
我只是问他长得什么样子
I just asked what he looked like.
再说
Besides,
就算我想跟他大搞一场
even if I decide to fuck his brains out,
又跟你有什么相干？
what business is that of yours?
为什么一定要说这种话？
- Why do you have to say that?
说什么？你知道什么 你这样说是存心气我 我这样说只是因为比较传神
- Say what?You know what.You say it just to irritate me.I say it because it's descriptive.
他不是那种会这样的男人
He doesn't strike me as a person who would go in for that kinda thing.
你总是低估我
Ann, you always underestimate me.
我不知道为什么会这样
I wonder why.
你怕让我们碰在一起
I think you're afraid to put us in the same room.
你怕他会被我吸引
You're afraid he'd be drawn to me.
我认为他不是你喜欢的那一型
Really, Cynthia,I don't think he's your type.
我喜欢的那一型？
My type?
你怎么知道，我喜欢那一型？
How would you know what my type is?
我才知道
Oh, I have a pretty good idea.
安，你什么都不知道
Ann, you don't have a clue.
我简直不明白，为什么要谈这个
Look, I don't even know
why we're discussin' this.
我是说我可以自己打电话找他
I mean, I'll just go over
and call him myself.
他没有电话
He doesn't have a phone.
那我就等他装了电话再打
Well, I'll call him when he does.
他不会装电话的，你说什么？
He won't.
What are you talkin' about?
他不喜欢电话，不会装的
He doesn't like to talk on the phone.
He's not getting a phone.
拜托
Oh, please.
请把这位大师的地址给我
OK, so give me the Zen master's address.
我找个理由去拜访一番
I'll think of a reason to stop by.
让我先和他说一声
Please, just let me talk to him first.
把地址给我就行了不必扯上你
Why? Just gimme the address.You won't even have to be involved.
我觉得这样不好
I don't feel right just giving you the
把地址给你，让你可以去...
address so you can go over there and...
去怎么样？
- And what?
做你会做的那种事
Do whatever it is you do.
「做你会做的那种事」
"Do whatever it is you do"?
听听你说话的语气
Listen to the way you talk.
我说得没什么不好，谢谢
- I talk fine.
- Thank you
我还在抽那根香烟
I was still smoking that.
你掉了什么东西吗？
What'd you lose?
那个珍珠耳环
That goddamn pearl earring.
我花了大笔钱买的
It cost me a fucking fortune.
一定是忘在什么地方了
I must've left it somewhere.
你打算送妈妈什么生日礼物？
So, what are you
gettin' Momma for her birthday?
我不知道，一张生日卡什么的
I don't know.
I'll get her a card or somethin'.
五十大寿只送张生日卡？
- A card for her 50th birthday?
有什么不对？
Yeah, what's wrong with that?
你是她生的，我想你至少...
Well, the woman gave birth to you.I think you might be givin' her...
不要说了好不好？
Will you stop? Jesus.
你这辈子至少有一次...好了
- I just thought that, you know, maybe...
- OK, Ann. OK.
这样好不好
How about this?
你去买一样好礼物
我付一半钱，好不好？
You get her something nice,
and I'll pay for half.
好，好
- All right?
- Fine. Fine.
好
Fine. OK.
对不起，我得上班去了
Now, if you'll pardon me,I have to go to work.
你自慰的地方最特别的在那里？
What is the most unusual location you've ever masturbated in?
有次我坐飞机
从洛杉矶到纽约
I, um...One time I was flying from Los Angeles to, um, to New York.
飞机上人很挤 我坐在中间位子
And I was... You know,it was a really crowded flight and I was...
没挑到窗边或走道的位子  那是唯一的一班飞机
I was sitting in the middle.I didn't get a window, I didn't get an aisle.
我觉得烦闷无聊，杂志也乏味
It was really funny,and I was... I was just bored.
我记得是在看一本女性杂志
My magazines were just boring.I think I had, like, a woman's magazine.
里面讨论不少关於性的问题
And they touch on a lot of sexual issuesand stuff.
我想，天啦...
And I was thinking to myself
我要的就是这个
"God, that's what I need. I need a little...
可以让我不再为旅行烦心
something to take my mind off this trip."
所以我就....你知道，乱想
So, I was just, you know,just thinking away
然後...我就...
and then I just...
在飞机上做了起来 就在另外两名乘客中间
I just did it on the plane.Just between these two people.
没有一个人知道
- Nobody knew.
你怎么可能一点不露出来
How were you able to not betray what was going on to the people around you?
比方说，我的肌肉很结实
Well, you know,
I have really strong muscles.
门没锁
It's open!
哈罗，安
- Hi!
- Hello, Ann.
希望我没有打扰你
- I hope I'm not botherin' you.
- No, no.
我该先通知一声的，你忙吗？
I would've phoned. You busy?
不忙，我可以等等再弄
No, no. I can finish later.
我是来看看，添了家俱的样子
I just wanted to see what the apartment looked like with furniture.
我怕没什么好看的
Yeah, well, I'm afraid
there's not much to see.
我是个精简主义者
I'm sort of cultivating
this minimalist vibe.
可以摆个书架
- You could use a bookshelf.
- Yeah?
你觉得吗？
Yeah, you think so?
这些全是图书馆借来的
They're... you know,
they're all library books.
这些是什么？
- What are these?
- Uh, those are videotapes.
录影带，我当然知道
I can see that.
是什么录影带？
Of what?
是我正在进行的一个私人研究
It's a personal project I've been workin' on.
什么样的私人研究？什么？
What kind of personal project?
什么样的私人研究？
- What?- What kind of personal project?
跟别人自己安排的没两样
Uh, a personal project
like anyone else's personal project.
我的只是更个人化一点，我想
Mine's just a little more personal, I guess.
唐娜是谁？什么？
Who's Donna?
带子上标著「唐娜」的名字
- What?
- Donna. It says "Donna" here on the tape.
唐娜是我在佛州认得的女孩子
Donna was a girl I knew in Florida.
你跟她约会过？
Oh, you went out with her?
没有，也不算啦
No, not really.
为什么所有的录影带上
Why do these tapes all have
都标著女人的名字？
women's names on 'em?
我比较喜欢访问女人
Well, I enjoy interviewing women more than men.
这是冰红茶，谢谢
- It's iced tea.- Thanks.
你要不要加宁檬片？
I'm sorry, do you want some lemon?
不用，这样很好
No, this is perfect.
这全是你访问的录影带？对
So, all of these are... are interviews, huh?
能不能看看
- Uh, yes.- Can we watch one?
不行，不行
No, I'd... No.
为什么不行？
Why not?
我答应过每一个被访问的对像
Well, I promised each of the subjects
除了我之外不会有别人看到
that no one would see the videotapes except for me.
访问都谈些什么呢？
What are the interviews about?
都是关於性的问题
The interviews are about sex.
性？
Sex?
性的什么问题？
What about sex?
所有关於性的问题
Uh, everything about sex.
比方说？
Like what?
她们做过些什么做些什么？
What they've done, what they do,
她们想要又不肯开口的是什么
what they want to do but are afraid to ask for,
即使对方要求也不肯的是什么
what they wouldn't do even if asked.
随便我想到什么都问
Anything I can think of.
小心你的冰水
Oh, your ice.
你只问她们各种问题？
- You just ask them questions?
- Yes.
她们都会回答？
And they answer 'em?
大部份都会回答
Yeah. Uh...
有时候只做不说
Mostly. Sometimes they do things.
和你吗？
不，只...只为了录影
- To you?
- No, uh... for the camera.
这实在是太...
- Graham, this is just so...
对不起，不该谈这个的
- I'm sorry this came up.
不，是我不对
No, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry this came up, and...
我不该谈这个，我得走了
I'm... I'm gonna go
给我吧，再见
Here, I'll take it.
他不想要你去找他
He doesn't want you to come over.
你这话是什么意思？
What do you mean?
你跟他说到我没有？没有
Did you tell him about me?- No, I didn't.
为什么没说？没空提起
- Why not?- Look, Cynthia, I didn't have time.
为什么？
- Well, why?
他很怪，你不要跟他扯上关系
John's right. He's strange and you don't wanna get involved with him.
怎么了？他向你求欢了吗？
What happened over there?
怎么突然说他「怪」起来了？
- Did he make a pass at you?- No.
他会把小狗淹死吗？
Well, what's this "strange" bullshit all of a sudden? Is he drownin' puppies?
不是这种事
It's nothin' like that, OK?
那是什么？他很危险？
Well, what? Is he dangerous?
不，实质上没有
No. Not physically.
那是什么呢？
Well, what, then?
我不想谈这个
- I don't wanna talk about it.
那你为什么打电话来？我不知道
- Then why did you call me?- I don't know.
辛蒂亚，我是约翰
- Hello?
- Cynthia, John.
今天不行，我另有安排
Not today. I've got other plans.
那什么时候呢？
Oh. Well, when, then?
请我去你家吃晚饭好不好？
How about inviting me over to dinner?
你知道我是什么意思...
You know what I mean.
我知道你是什么意思
Yeah, I know what you mean.
门没锁
- It's open.
- Hi.
- Hello.
请问有什么事吗？我叫辛蒂亚.毕夏普
- Can I help you?- I'm Cynthia Bishop.
我们见过吗？
Do I know you? I don't...
我是安的妹妹
I'm Ann Millaney's sister.
那个很外向的
The extrovert.
这样说是她心情好的时候
She must have been in a good mood.
通常她都说我很粗鲁
She usually calls me loud.
她也说过
Yeah, she called you that, too.
你有什么贵干？
So, uh, what are you doin' here?
要我走吗？
- You want me to leave?
你来有什么事呢？
- No, I just wanna know why you're here.
安是我姐姐，姐妹间无话不谈
Well, like I said, Ann is my sister.
其馀的你可想而知了
Sisters talk. You can imagine the rest.
我想我最好不要批评
No, I think it's probably better
if I don't characterise that conversation
我没听到的谈话
that I didn't hear.
我不知道你或者
I don't have any idea, really, what you
安会怎么说我和说别的
or Ann said about me or anything else.
要不要来点冰红茶？好
- Do you want some iced tea?
- Sure.
我没有宁檬了
I don't have any lemons.
上次和安见面，她离开的时候
The last time I saw Ann she left here very confused
有点搞不清楚，又很不开心
I'd say, and upset.
她现在还是一样
She still is.
你今天来是不是要我...
So, are you here to make me feel bad
为了让她难过而觉得难过？
for makin' her feel bad?No.
她有没有说，她为什么不高兴？
- She didn't tell you why she was upset?
- No.
我不懂你为什么会来
So, I don't understand what made you wanna come here.
我想安不会把我说得很好的
I can't imagine Ann painted a very flattering portrait of me.
谈到男人我从来不相信安的话
Yeah, well, see, um, I don't really listen to Ann when it comes to men.
你看看约翰，我的老天
I mean, look at John, for Christ's sake.
你跟他以前是同学吧
But then, you went to school
with him, didn't you?
恐怕还是好朋友
You're probably friends or somethin'.
不是，我想约翰很会骗人
No.
No, I think John is a liar.
我想你说得对
I think you're right.
我来是想弄清楚
So come on, I came all the way over here
到底是什么把安给吓坏了
to find out what got Ann so spooked.
告诉我出什么事？
Why don't you tell me what happened?
吓坏了？
"Spooked"?
是这些录影带把安吓坏了
The videotapes are what got Ann so spooked.
我想我明白了
I think I get it.
你明白什么？
Oh, yeah? What do you get?
能吓倒安的一定和性爱有关
If Ann got freaked out by these,they must be somethin' sexual.
是你在做爱的录影带吗？
Are these tapes of you havin' sex with these girls?
不，不完全是
No, not exactly.
是就是，不是就不是
Either you are or you aren't.
到底是不是？
Which is it?
你何不让我替你录影？
- Why don't you let me tape you?
要我做什么？
- Doin' what?
说话
Talking.
说什么？
About what?
关於性的问题  你的性爱史，你的性癖好
About sex. Your sexual history,sexual preferences.
你怎么会认为我肯谈这些？
What makes you think I'd discuss that?
没什么
Nothing.
你只问我一些问题？只问你问题
- And you just wanna ask me questions?- I just wanna ask you questions.
没有别的？对
- That's all?
- That's all.
你用这种方法求得满足？录女人谈性的问题
Is this how you get off? Tapin' women talkin' about their sexual experiences?
不错会有别人看到这卷录影带吗？
- Yes.- Would anyone else see the tape?
绝对不会，除了我没有别人
Absolutely not. Nobody else sees the tapes except for me.
要多久时间？
How long will it take?
随你的便，有人只用了三分钟
Well, that depends on you.
One woman used up only three minutes.
还有个用了三卷两小时的带子
And another used three two-hour tapes.
我们怎么开始？
How do we start?
我打开录影机，你说话
I turn on the camera and you start talking.
我坐著还是站著？
Do I sit or stand?
随你高兴
- What do you prefer?
我喜欢坐著
- I'd prefer to sit.
好了吗？
Are you ready?
好了，我正在录
OK, I'm recording.
告诉我你叫什么名字
- So tell me your name.
辛蒂亚.派翠丝.毕夏普
- Cynthia... Patrice... Bishop.
用你平常的声调说
- You can speak in a normal voice.- OK.
请描述一下，你第一次性经验
So, describe for me your first sexual experience.
第一次性经验，还是第一次性交
First sexual experience or first time I had intercourse?
第一次性经验
- First sexual experience.- Sexual experience.
我当时是...八岁
I was... uh... eight.
是不是这种事...？
And, uh...Is this the kinda thing that...? Yeah, OK.
我当时八岁
I was eight years old, and, um,
麦可.葛林也是八岁
Michael Green, who was also eight
他问我能不能看我尿尿
asked if he could watch me take a pee.
我说只要也让我看他就可以
And I said he couldif I could watch him take one, too.
我们到我家後面的树林里
So we went to the woods behind my house.
我觉得他是临阵退缩了
And I got this feeling he was chickenin'
因为他一直说「女士优先」
out cos he kept sayin' "Ladies first!"
我拉下小裤裤尿了起来
So I pulled down my little panties and urinated,
我还没嘘完他就逃了
and he ran away before I even finished.
事後你们两人有没再谈起这事
Was it a topic of conversation between you after that?
没，那整个夏天他都躲著我
No! He kind of avoided me for the rest of the summer,
後来他们家搬走了
and then his family moved away.
搬去了克利夫兰
To Cleveland, actually.
真差劲
What a shame.
什么时候你才见到男人那话儿
When did you finally see a penis?
我十四岁那年
When I was 14.
你当时有什么感想？
So, what'd you think?
和你原先想像的一样吗？
Was it what you expected it to be?
不，不完全一样
No. Not really. I...
我原以为是...
I didn't... I sorta pictured it, um...
我没想到那玩意儿会有青筋和线
I didn't think it would have
veins or ridges or anything.
我原以为很光滑像根试管
I just thought it would be smooth,
like a test tube.
现在想起，也太怪异了
It's weird, thinking about it now.
那个器官本身看来好像...
The... organ itself seemed like a separate thing,
是个独立的个体
a separate entity to me.
等到他掏出来，让我看让我摸时
I mean, when he finally pulled it out and I could look at it and touch it,
我都忘了，後面还连著一个人
I forgot that there was a guy attached to it.
那家伙一开口，还真吓了我一跳
I remember literally being startled when the guy spoke to me.
他说什么？
- What did he say?
他说我用手摸得他很舒服
- He said my hand felt good.
後来呢？
Then what happened?
我开始把我的手动来动去
And...Then I started movin' my hand
他就不再说话了
and then he stopped talkin'.
约翰，我是辛蒂亚
- Yeah?
- John, Cynthia.
你电话怎么接得进来的？
- How'd you get through?
我骗珍娜说我是安
I told Janet I was Ann.
她相信了？
Ah. She bought it?
显然是信了吧，我说...
Well, obviously.
我要见你
Look... I want to see you.
什么时候？
- Ah. When?
就是现在
Right now.
我有当事人在等著
I don't know if I can do that.
I got a client waiting.
我已经放过他一回鸽子了  这下又得天下大乱
I've already rescheduled him once.
I'd have to do some heavy-duty juggling.
要干就快干，马上过来
Then get those balls in the air
and get your butt over here.
珍尼
- Yes, sir?
- Janet.
我要你再改下柯南的约谈时间
Listen, I want you to reschedule Kirkland.
我知道
I know, I know.
看他能不能在礼拜一来
See if he can come in Monday, any time.
随时都可以，告诉他...
Tell him, uh... Tell him, uh...
跟他说是...我家有急事
- Family crisis. Family crisis.
- OK.
我会从後门走
- I'll slip out the back.
- Yes, sir.
All right. Bye.
你要不要我脱掉裙子？
Would you like me to take my skirt off?
随你
If you wish.
你没有穿内衣
You're not wearing any underwear.
你喜不喜欢我这样子？喜欢
Do you like the way I look?
Yes.
你觉得我漂亮吗？漂亮
Do you think I'm pretty?
比安还漂亮？
Prettier than Ann?
你们两个不一样
Different.
约翰和安不再同床了
John and Ann don't have sex any more.
这话是他告诉你的吗？
Is that what he tells you?
不用他告诉我
He doesn't have to tell me.
你今天真是热情如火
You're on fire today.
对
Yes.
你可以走了
You can go now.
什么样的问题？
What kind of questions?
和...性有关的问题
Questions... about... sex.
他到底问些什么嘛？
Well, what did he ask, exactly?
我不想一五一十告诉你
Well, I don't wanna tell you, exactly.
你让个陌生人录下你的性生活
You let a total stranger record your sexual life
却不能告诉你的亲姐姐
but you won't tell your own sister?
就是...
- Apparently.
他有没有要你脱衣服？
- Did he ask you to take your clothes off?
有没有要我脱衣服？没有
Did he ask me to take my clothes off?
No, he didn't.
那你有没有脱呢？
- Did you take your clothes off?
我脱了
- Yes.
辛蒂亚，干嘛？
- Cynthia!
- What?
你为什么要做这种事？
- Why did you do that?
因为我想脱呀
- Because I wanted to.
为什么？
- But why did you want to?
我要他看我
- Because I wanted him to see me.
你疯了
You're crazy.
他可以播映出来
He could be bouncin' it off some satellite.
让美国南部色狼全来看你
- Some horny old men could be watchin'.
他不会这样做的
- Ann! He wouldn't do that.
你怎么晓得反正现在也来不及了，对吧？
- You don't know that for sure.
- Well, it's too late now, isn't it?
他有没有碰你？
- Did he touch you?
没有
- No.
你有没有碰他？没有
- Did you touch him?- No.
那有没有谁碰了谁呢？
Did anybody touch anybody?
有的
Well, yes.
难道说...
Don't tell me.
可不会，难道..你没干那事吧
Don't tell me. Don't tell me. You didn't.
我做了  真的？
- I did.- You didn't.
我做了，做了
- I did!
我的天啦，辛蒂亚
- Oh, my God. Cynthia!
你麻烦大了
You're in trouble.
听听你的话，像老妈一样
Listen to you. You sound like Momma.
你在说什么呀？
What are you talkin' about?
老天，辛蒂亚
God, Cynthia.
我连在约翰面前也不做那种事
- I couldn't do that in front of John.
你是根本就不会做 你甚至还不认得他 我倒觉得我认得
- You couldn't do it, period.- I mean, you don't even know him.
- I feel like I do.
你不能信任他，他有点变态
You don't.You can't trust him. He's perverted.
你干嘛这么紧张？
I don't understand why this freaks you out so much.
又不是你做了什么，是我呀  我都不担心，你担心什么？
You didn't do it, I did, and if it doesn't
bother me, why should it bother you?
我不想再谈这个  好呀，那就不要说了
- I don't wanna talk about it.- OK, then, don't.
你是个杀手吗？
Are... are you an assassin?
你说什么？
- Excuse me?
你不过是个跑腿的
- You're just an errand boy,
杂货店老板派来收帐的
sent by the grocer to collect the bill.
我在学马龙白兰度，很棒吧？
It's my Brando. That's pretty good,isn't it? Marlon Brando.
很棒，对不起
It's great. Pardon me.
我想我们　要分开一段时间
该在那头多待一阵
OK. I was thinkin' we needed time apart.
Maybe you should be there for a while.
你为什么不装个电话答录机？
Hi. So, why don't you get
an answering machine?
这里有电话
- There's a phone here.
老打不进来
- It's busy.
继续打
Well, why don't you keep tryin'?OK.
买的是这个
- Well, here it is.
什么？
- What is it?
一件长衫
- It's a sundress.
看起来像块桌布
- Looks like a tablecloth.
才不呢  为什么买没袖子的长衫呢？
- It does not. - Why would she want a sundress?
她又有老人斑，又有静脉瘤
She's got spots on her shoulders and varicose veins.
你将来有一天也会有的
- Well, missy thing, so will you someday.
到那时候，我就不穿这种衣服
- When I do, I won't wear sundresses.
等一下
- God, Cynthia...
- Hold on.
辛蒂亚，我是约翰
- Bayou.
- Cynthia, John.
时间选得真好，你老婆在这里
- Would you like to speak with your wife?
她到那里去做什么？
- What's she doin' there?
让我看我们送你丈母娘的礼物
Showing me a present she and I are buying your mother-in-law.
好极了，什么时候可以见你？
Oh. Great. So, when can I see you?
我怕不能像上回那样激烈了
I don't know. I'm not sure I can
duplicate the intensity I had the other day.
试试何妨？
Nothin' wrong with trying.
我怕我老姐不会同意的
I don't think my sister would agree.
是不是不要我再打电话给你？
Do you want me to stop calling?
我再打给你，好吗？完毕
- Look, I'll call you. OK?
- Roger.
真巧啊，我穿红的你也穿红的
真是有缘吧
This is too much. I'm wearing red, you're
wearing red. That's quite a coincidence...
我已经结婚了
- Look, I'm married.
- Really?
很在意这点吗？
Are you very married?
够在意的了
- Married enough.
- Oh. Oh.
那也没什么关系嘛
我是来看我妹妹的
- I see. Well, that shouldn't stop us...
- I'm just here to see my sister. OK?
真的，谁是你妹妹？
Oh, really?Who's your sister?
她结婚了没有？
Is she married?
我该付多少钱？
So, um, what's my share of the dress?
三十二块五毛
- 32.50.
- It's a nice dress.
这件衣服不错
我也觉得不错
好像块桌布
- Thanks. I thought so, too.
- Looks like a tablecloth.
零钱就不要找了
Keep the change. And, Ann, don't worryabout the dress.
我相信她会喜欢这件衣服的
I'm sure she'll like it.
你就要走了吗？
Yeah. I think it'll...
Oh, you have to go? OK. Goodbye.
再见，我会打电话给你
I'll see you later. I'll call you!
再见
Bye.
约翰
John?
Mm?
约翰
- John?
上礼拜一我打过电话到办公室
I called you last Monday at 3:30
三点半左右他们说你不在
and they said you weren't in.
记得你去了那里吗？
Do you remember where you were?
礼拜一？
On Monday?
上礼拜一？
Uh... Last Monday?
我中饭吃晚了
Oh, I had a late lunch.
和谁一起吃的中饭？
So, who'd you have lunch with?
我一个人
I ate by myself.
有什么不对吗？
- Is there somethin' wrong?
你是不是外面有了女人？
- Are you havin' an affair?
我的老天爷
Jesus Christ!
我一个人晚了点去吃中饭
I have a late lunch by myself
就是在搞什么人？
and now I'm fuckin' somebody?
有没有呢？没有
- Well, are you?
- No, I'm not.
你这么指责我，我很生气
God, I'm offended
at the accusation. Come on.
要是我说对了，我希望能知道
If I'm right, I wanna know.
别骗我，我是会火大
I don't want you to lie. I'd be upset,
可是要是你骗我，我会更火大
but I'd be more upset if you lied to me.
没有什么好知道的
Well, there's nothin' to know.
要是你骗我，我不知会多火大
I can't tell you
how upset I'll be if you lie to me.
这叫偏执狂
This is paranoia.
要真有人是偏执狂的话
I mean... if anybody should be paranoid,
也该是我
I should be.
每次我一要碰你
Here, every time I try to touch you,
你就躲得像我一身臭屎似的
you act as if I'm dipped in shit.
有很多女人都会想有个年轻的
I think there are a lot of women
out there that'd be glad to have
喜欢女人的男人收入高的
a young, straight male
makin' a pretty good living
陪她们躺在床上
beside 'em in bed with a... with a hard-on.
而且还是在兴奋状态的 我妹妹就是一个，我的老天爷
- My sister, for one.- For God's sake, Ann.
就是她吧？
- Is that who it is?
安，我可没搞你妹妹
- Ann, I'm not fucking your sister.
我并不觉得她好看
I don't find her that attractive,for one thing.
这话是安慰我吗？
- Is that supposed to comfort me?
不是！我只是说 你不跟我做爱，我也没乱想
- No, I'm just saying.-I'm just saying I didn't get paranoid
when you didn't wanna make love to me.
我不会就假设你有了外遇
I could have assumed that you didn't want
to because you were having an affair.
我没有
- I'm not.
很好，我也没有
- Well, I'm not either. Now, come on.
那我为什么不相信你呢？
- Then why don't I believe you?
太荒唐了，也许等你有了证据
- Oh, look. This is ridiculous.- Maybe when you have evidence...
你是说还有证据？
- There's evidence?
我不是这个意思
That's not what I'm saying.
我们不该连话都不谈
I'm just
saying that we shouldn't not ever talk,
不能只凭猜测和直觉来说我
just don't give me conjecture and intuition.
总是一付律师的嘴脸
- Always a lawyer.- Goddamn right.
能这样说吗？法官大人
I mean, can you imagine? "Your Honour,
I'm positive the man is guilty."
我相信他有罪，只是没证据
好了，好了
- "I can't place him at the scene..."- All right.
好了，你意思说清楚了，好了
- "But I have this strong feeling..."
- All right. You made your point. OK.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我只是最近压力太大...
I'm just under a lot of pressure
因为柯南那件案子
with this... this Kirkland thing.
这是我做合夥人後第一件大案
I mean, you know
it's my first big case as junior partner.
我忙了一整天，回到家来
I work all day and I come home.
只想看你
I look forward to seeing you.
我觉得很伤心
你这样冤枉我
It hurts that you'd accuse me like that.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我整天无所事事
I've just got all this time
on my hands, and I just sit around
所以空坐在那里胡思乱想
and start inventing these,like, intricate scenarios.
我又不想浪费时间 所以就相信了我想出来的事情
And then I don't want to have wasted
all my time, so I wanna believe 'em.
心理治疗没有用吗？约翰，我不知道
- Isn't therapy helpin' at all?
- Oh, John, I don't know.
我觉得谈我的问题是很笨的事
I just feel so stupid sittin'
talkin' about my little problems
因为世界上还有孩子在挨饿
when I knowthose poor children are starving.Well...
就算停止心理治疗
Quitting your therapy's not gonna...
也不等於能饱非洲的孩童
not gonna feed the children in Ethiopia.
我知道
I know.
你以前从来不说「干」那个字
You never used to say the word "fucking".
我操！
Fuck.
真笨，我不相信你真做那种事
It's so stupid, I have a hard time
believing you did it.
那有什么愚笨的
- What's so stupid about it?
- Well, you...
你甚至还不认得那小子呢
- You don't even know the guy.
- Well, you know him.
你认得他呀，他是你朋友  你想他可以信任吗？
He's a friend of yours.
Do you think he can be trusted?
我不知道
I don't know.
我不知道，照你所说的...
I don't know From what you've told me,
我真的不知道
I don't know.
我早该想到的，他来的时候
I shoulda known when he showed up dressed like
穿得像是殡丁馆的人
some undertaker for the art world.
我喜欢他的衣服
I like the way he dresses.
万一录影带流进别人手里呢？
What if this tape gets into the wrong hands?
别人手里？
"The wrong hands"? John, we are not
又不是什么军事机密
talking about military secrets here.
那些录影带只是让他用来 满足他自己的
They're just tapes he makes
so he can sit around and get off.
他没和她们发生关系
And he doesn't have sex with any of them?
只是谈话而已
They just talk?
他们只是坐著聊天
They just sit around and talk.
要是他们有什么的话，我倒了解
I could almost understand it
if he had sex with them. I mean, almost.
他为什么不买杂志和小电影呢？
Why doesn't he just buy some magazines
or some porno movies or somethin'?
他要了解对方
要彼此能有互动关系
Doesn't work. He has to know the people.
He has to be able to interact with them.
互动关系？
Interact?
真搞不懂是什么意思....
Whatever that means.
非一定要在他面前自慰吗？
Did you have to masturbate in front of him?
我喜欢，你跟安一样大惊小怪！
I felt like it. Goddamn. You and Ann
make such a big deal out of this.
你告诉了安？
她是我姐姐
- You told Ann about this?
- She is my sister.
我真希望你没说为什么？
- I tell her almost everything.
- I wish you hadn't.
这种事我情愿她不知道
It's just something I'd prefer
she didn't have to know about.
她已经成年，可以应付得了的
- She's a grown-up. She can handle it.
- Ann...
安实在是很...
保守
- Ann is just very...
- Hung up.
那样做实在不聪明
当然罗
- It just wasn't a smart thing to do.
- Oh, God!
你有没有让他签什么文件
Did you sign any sort of paper,
or did he have a contract with you
说他不能播映这些录影带的？
saying that he wouldn't
broadcast these things?
抱歉，没有
No, sir.
你知道你没有任何法律保
You realise you have no recourse legally?
这可不是好玩的
这不是开玩笑的，辛蒂亚
It's not funny. It's not funny, Cynthia.
那些录影带说不定就会出现别处
These tapes could show up anywhere.
不会的，我信任他
They won't. I trust him.
你信任他？真好笑
You trust him? That's funny.
不错，我信任他 比对你要信任多
Yeah, I do.A hell of a lot more than I trust you.
什么意思？
- What do you mean?
就是我说的那个意思
- Just what I said.
要相信你还不如相信他
I'd trust him before I'd trust you.
你这话太伤我心了
你跟你的小姨子乱搞又骗人
- It hurts that you say that to me.
- You're fucking your wife's sister.
起码我知道你骗人
You're a liar. But at least I know that.
我知道我是第二等差劲的人
I know, I know. Second-lowest formof human being.
也是第一等
And the first.
你说什么呀？没什么 你也骗了安 不错，可是...
- What are you talking about?
- Nothing. You're lying to Ann, too.
我并没在神和众人面前立誓 说永远对安忠实
Yeah, right, but I didn't take a vow in front
of God and everyone to be faithful to Ann.
我们到底要不要做爱呀？
Look, are we gonna do it or not?
说老实话...不要
我改变主意了，我不该打给你
Actually... no. I've changed my mind.
I shouldn't have called.
我既已经来了
Well, I'm here now.
就得要做点什么
I need to do somethin'.
要不要帮我收拾房间？
Would you like to help me straighten up?
这里就没有一把椅子能坐吗？
Jesus!
Is there one chair
in this place that works?
你何不到别处去坐？
Well, why don't you
go sit somewhere else?
得了吧，约翰
Come on, John. You should be happy.
我们交往这么久还没被安发现
We've gone this far without Ann findin'out.
也该高兴了
I'm makin' it real easy on you.
我给你方便只要你走出去
- Just walk out of here.
是他让你这样的吗？
- Did he put you up to this?
谁呀？葛伦
- Who?
- Graham.
不是，他没有 我不　要别人来叫我怎么做
No, he didn't put me up to this. Jesus,
I don't need people to tell me what to do.
只是我想通了，现在你请吧
I've just been thinkin', that's all.Now just... leave.
也许我不想走
Maybe I don't wanna leave.
也许我想和你谈谈
Maybe I wanna talk.
我们没什么好谈的
John, we don't have
anything to talk about.
你说得对
Yeah, you're right.
事情越来越复杂了
Things are gettin' complicated.
不对，其实是变得非常简单
No, they're gettin' real simple.
门没锁
It's open!
要不要喝点什么？
Want something to drink?
好，谢谢
Yeah, thanks.
我没有冰红茶了
I'm sorry, I don't have any iced tea left.
约翰和辛蒂亚搞上了
John and Cynthia have been... fucking.
我知道
Yes, I know.
你知道？知道
- You know?
- Yes.
你怎么知道的？
How did you know?
她在录影的时候说的
She said it on her tape.
多谢你告诉我，感激不尽
Thanks for telling me.
I really appreciate it.
最近我又没见到你
Well, I... I haven't seen you.
而且即使见到，我也不会说的
And I don't think I would've told you
even if I had seen you.
为什么？
Why not?
因为实在不该由我来说
Because it's not really my place.
我的生活简直一团糟
My life is shit.
真狗屎
It's just shit.
什么都跟我所想的不一样
Nothing's what I thought it was.
约翰是个狗杂种
John's a bastard.
我们来录影吧
Let's make a videotape.
我觉得这样不太好
No, I...
为什么不好？
- I don't think that's a good idea.
- Why not?
不是你脑筋正常时会想做的事
Because I don't think it's a choice that
you'd make in a normal frame of mind.
你知道什么脑筋正常不正常？
And what would you know
about a normal frame of mind?
这倒问得好
That's a good question.
要怎么准备？
- So, what do you have to do to get ready?
- Uh...
装上带子，打开录影机
Load a tape and turn on the camera.
来吧
Do it.
我说...你那来的钱买...
So, where do you get your money from,
买录影带和其他那些东西？
for rent, and tapes, and stuff like that?
从我床垫底下拿的
Underneath my mattress.
钱用光了之後呢？
And what are you gonna do
when this money runs out?
用不完的
It won't.
你这样舒服吗？
Are you comfortable there?
很舒服
Yeah, I'm comfortable.
好，我开始录了
OK, I'm recording.
告诉我你叫什么名字
Tell me your name.
安.毕夏普.梅南尼
Ann Bishop Millaney.
马格丽特，我是约翰  你今天有没见到安？
Margaret. Hi, it's John. Fine.
Listen, have you seen Ann at all today?
她留书出走了吗？
This afternoon?
Uh... Well, no, I just...
她回来了，再见，没事，谢了
She's home. Bye-bye.
Everything's fine. Thanks. Bye.
你让我担心死了
Thank God. You had me worried sick.
我回来发现门开著，车不见了
I come home,
the door is open, the car is gone.
我以为你被那个疯子绑架了
I thought you'd been
abducted by some mad fucker.
你没事吧？
- Are you all right?
我要离婚
- I want out of this marriage.
什么？
What?
我要和你离婚
I... want... out... of this marriage.
为什么？
Why?
「为什么？」
你还问我为什么？
You're asking me why?
我是你丈夫，你要离婚
I'm married to you
and you want out of this marriage.
我当然要问啦
I think you could tell me that.
去你的！
Fuck you. Fuck you.
好吧
All right.
你到那里去了？
- Can you tell me where you went?
- I drove around.
我开车乱转，然後到葛伦家
- Then I went over to Graham's.
- Graham's?
葛伦
Graham.
他妈的那狗娘养的！
Goddamn that son of a bitch!
背後伤人的小人还自称诚实
The backstabbin' son of a...
Oh, Mr Honesty, huh?
真是正直之士！
Mr Apostle of Truth!
我知道你没跟他上床
Well, I know you didn't fuck him.
你有没有拍录影带呢？
Did you make one of
these goddamn videotapes?
你看著我
Annie... answer me, goddammit.
回答我的话，他妈的，有没有？
Goddammit, answer me. Did you?
有，我拍了
- Yes, I did.
- Ah!
你敢伤他！
Don't you touch him!
你到这里来干嘛？
John? What the hell are you doing here?
What are you doing?
好，我开始录了
OK, I'm recording.
你叫什么名字？
Tell me your name.
安.毕夏普.梅南尼
Ann... Bishop... Millaney.
你想谈些什么呢？
So, what do you wanna talk about?
你通常让她们谈什么？
- What do you usually talk about?
性的问题
- Sex.
好，就谈性的问题
OK. Let's talk about sex.
你常有性行为吗？
Do you have sex?
没，不常有
Not very often, no.
有的话通常是谁主动呢
When you do, who usually initiates it?
是他
He does.
你觉得满足吗？
Is the sex satisfying?
我不知道
I don't know.
我不知道，我不懂你的意思
I don't know. I don't know what you mean.
你有没有达到高潮？
Do you have orgasms?
我想没有
I don't think so.
我不能确定
I mean, I guess, since I'm not sure,
that I've never had one.
所以我想必是从来没有过
你有没想过除了你丈夫之外
Have you ever thought about having sex
和别的男人做爱？
with someone other than your husband?
这下来了
Here we go.
不要拍了好吧？
- Why don't we stop- No.
不行，我不想停下来
I don't wanna stop.
有没想过和别的男人做爱呢？
Have you ever thought about having sex
with someone other than your husband?
想过
I've thought about it.
那有没有真的那样做呢？
- Did you act on it?
没有
- No.
为什么没有？
Why not?
因为辛蒂亚是那样想的 我讨厌和她有同样感觉
Because that's how Cynthia thinks.
I hate it when I have feelings that she has.
我之不愿意想男人 就因为那是她的想法
It bothers me when I think about men,
because I know that's the way she thinks.
你想到什么样的男人呢？
What other men have you thought about?
我想的是你
I thought about you.
你有没有想过我？
- Have you thought about me?
想过
- Yes.
你想些什么？
What did you think?
想你在高潮时是什么样子
I thought about what you would
look like having an orgasm.
我倒想知道我高潮时什么样子
I'd like to know
what I look like havin' an orgasm.
你能做到吗？
Can you do that?
让女人达到高潮？
Give a woman an orgasm?
可以
Yes.
你能为我做吗？
Could you do that for me?
不行
- No.
为什么不行？
- Why not?
因为我不能
Because I can't.
是不能还是不愿意？
- Can't or won't?
- I can't because I won't.
我不能是因为我不愿意的缘故
你说你并不真是性无能
- You said you weren't always impotent.
不错
- No. Yeah, that's correct.
所以你也跟人家做过爱？
- So you have had sex.
是的
- Yes.
结果呢？是差得让你失去兴趣
So, what happened?
Was it so bad it turned you off, or...?
我的问题不在那里
- No, that wasn't the problem.
那问题在那里？
- What was the problem?
问题在我自己
I was the problem. I was a...
我以为总忍不住会说谎
I was a pathological liar.
我应该说我现在还是这样
Or I am, I should say.
说谎是...
The lying is...
说谎就像酗酒始终想戒掉
Lying is like alcoholism,you're continually recovering.
原来是这样？
So that's it?
你是骗我的？
You lied?
那只是一部份而巳
- That was part of it.
还有什么呢？
- So, what else happened?
在那时候
Well, at that time, uh... I...
我通常不以语言来表达感情
I used to express my feelings nonverbally,
这样常会吓到别人
and often scared people
尤其是和我亲近的人
that were close to me.
你现在还是那样吗？
Are you still like that?
不是
No.
你打算从此不再做爱吗？
So you're never gonna make love again?
我并没有任何计划什么的
I don't... I haven't made any plans, so...
如果你爱我的话你会不会？
- If you were in love with me, would you?
- I'm not in love with you.
我没爱上你，若是呢？
- But if you were?
这个问题我不能回答
- I can't answer that.
为什么？我说过了
- Why not?- I told you.
我不明白 我是说不要再想性的问题
- But I don't understand.
- Ann, forget about the sex, you know? I...
我已经不是以前的我了
I'm not the same person that I was even remotely, you know.
很多地方都不一样了
I'm different in so many ways.
这影响到我和别人的关系
It'd have a profound effect on the way that
I relate to other people, communicate.
或是沟通  我是说她和我交谈的情形  恐怕再也不可能...
This, for instance. The way she and I are
talking, it could never have been possible.
她？她和我交谈的情形？
"She"? "The way she...
she and I are talking"?
她？「她」是谁？
对不起...我是..我只是
- "She"? Who's "she"?
- I'm sorry, I was...
她是伊莉莎白吗？
- That isn't what I was...
- She's Elizabeth? Is that who it is?
是不是约翰提起过的那个人？
Is that the girl that John talked about?
是不是她？
Is that who it is?
我想是的  那你现在还和她有连络了？
- I guess. I... I'm sorry.
- So, you're still in contact with her?
和伊莉莎白？没有
- With Elizabeth?- No. I'm...
你想伊莉莎白对这些录影带
What do you think Elizabeth
会有什么看法？
is gonna think about all these videotapes?
我想她不会很了解吧
I can't imagine her bein' too understanding.
你会告诉她这些录影带的事吧
But you're gonna tell her about them,
因为你已经不再说谎了
right, since you don't lie any more?
我说了我不知道到底会怎么做
As I said, I don't know
what I'm gonna do, exactly.
也许我什么也不做
I mean... perhaps I won't do anything.
你回这里来就是为考虑这事？
So, you just came back here
so that you could think about it?
我之所以搬回这里来是为了.
No, I moved back here for some...
想让事情告一结束
A sense of closure, you know?
算是一种解决
Resolution of some sort.
我希望对我来说很重要的某人  能了解这点
I wanted somebody who was very
important to me to understand that.
这太可怜了
That's... That's pathetic.
你不能就...
I mean, you can't just...
Oh, my God, Graham.
天啦，葛伦，你不能...
就这样去找她
You just can't walk up to her
and show her you've changed
像送礼似的告诉她你变了
like it's some gift or somethin'.
看看你变成了什么样子
And look what you've changed into.
九年
过了九年只得到这种结果
Nine years. Nine years.
And this is what you come up with.
你这辈子就打算这样下去吗？
Is this what you wanna be
the rest of your life?
你为什么做这些？
Why are you doin' this?
你能告诉我吗？
Can you tell me that?
你为什么这种对待你自己
Why are you doin' this to yourself?
你回不回答我？拜托，不要这样
- Are you gonna answer me?
- Please, don't do that.
为什么不？
- Why not?
- Don't do that.
你为什么录下女人谈性的问题
I wanna ask a few questions, like why
do you tape women talkin' about sex?
你为什么做这种事？告诉我
Why do you do that?
Can you tell me why?
说话呀
Come on. I'm just gonna keep askin'.
我不觉得你反客为主很有意思
I don't find turning the tables
very interesting.
我倒觉得很好
Well, I do. Tell me why, Graham.
告诉我为什么
- Why?
- What?
你要我告诉你什么呢？
What? What do you want me to tell you?
告诉我原因，为什么？
"Tell me why?" Why?
你根本不知道我是什么人
Ann, you don't even know who I am. You
don't have the slightest idea who I am.
难道说我该倾吐平生种种
Am I supposed to recount all the points
in my life leading up to this moment
希望能首尾一贯
and just hope that it's coherent,
that it makes some sort of sense to you?
让你了解？我自己都搞不懂呢！你知道，那是我的生活
It doesn't make any sense to me.
You know, I was there.
我都搞不清，我到底是什么人
I don't have the slightest idea who I am,
还要我向你说明什么？
and I'm supposed
to be able to explain it to you?
为什么？你倒告诉我为什么
And why? You tell me why.
为什么？我该对你解释我自己？
Why do I have to explain myself to you?
因为我也许能帮你
Because maybe I can help you.
帮我什么？
- Help me with what?
- Your problem.
解决你的问题  我的问题？我有问题吗？
My problem? Do I have a problem?
我在这里见到约翰辛蒂亚  还有你之後
I look around me in this town and I see
John and Cynthia and you, and I...
我觉得自己比你们健康多了
I feel comparatively healthy.
你有问题
You've got a problem.
你说得对
You're right.
我有一大堆问题
I've got a lot of problems.
可是那些是我的问题
But they belong to me.
你以为问题是你的其实不然
You think they're yours, but they're not.
每个走进那扇门的人
Everybody that walks in that door
都成为你问题的一部份
becomes part of your problem.
每个你认得的人也一样
Anybody that comes in contact with you.
我不想成为你问题的一部份  可是我已经没法脱身
I didn't wanna be part of your problem, but I am.
我要跟我丈夫离婚
I'm leavin' my husband,
也许这是迟早的事  可是事实是，我现在下的决定
and maybe I would have anyway,
but the fact is that I'm doin' it now.
而部份原因就在於你
And part of it's because of you.
你影响到我的生活
You've had an effect on my life.
这种事不该发生的
This isn't supposed to happen.
我花了九年的时间来构ZZ生活  就为避免这种事
I've spent nine years structuring my life
so that this didn't happen.
我从来没对你说过这件事  因为你受不了这种打击的
You know, I never told you this,
cos I knew it'd crush you.
可是现在...
But now...
我跟伊莉莎白睡过觉
I fucked Elizabeth.
那是你们俩散伙之前的事  在你们俩失和之前
Before you broke up.Before you were havin' trouble, even.
她不是圣女
She's no saint.
她在床上功夫很好
She was good in bed.
她倒是真能保密
She could keep a secret.
对她，我能说的就只这点了
That's about all I can say about her.
柯南先生办公室
- Kirkland's office.
我是约翰，找柯南先生
- John Millaney for Brian Kirkland.
请等一等
- Just one moment, please.- All right.
我一向说工作是最重要的
Anyway, as I've always said,work is critical.
没有婚姻，我能很快乐
I can be happy without a marriage,
可是没有工作的话
but if you take away my work
那可不一样了
that's different.
安要是不能了解这点
And if Ann can't handle that...
那是她的问题
- Well, that's her problem.
迪  老板要见你
- Mr Millaney?- Yeah.- Mr DeForest would like to see you.
好的，等下就去
All right. In a minute. I'm on with a client.
他说请你马上去好
- He said immediately.- All right. Jesus.
柯南先生请我告诉你...
Mr Kirkland asked me to inform you
他决定另请高明了
he's obtained representation elsewhere,
有什么话可以由我转达
and that if you have a message
for Mr Kirkland to leave it with me.
不用了
- No message.
- All right, Mr Millaney.
笨蛋！
Fool!
我希望他搞清楚状况
Hope he knows what he's doin'.
迪老板在等你啦
- Mr Millaney?- Yeah?- Mr DeForest is waiting.
告诉他我马上就到
- All right. Tell him I'll be in in a minute.
老天，老家伙以为天底下
Jesus, the old man thinks that
只有打高尔夫球最重要
the world revolves around a game of golf.
待会儿见，我得去见迪老板了
I'll catch up to you at the courts.
I'd better go talk to DeForest.
不用，一瓶就够了，谢谢你啦
Oh, no, just one's fine, thanks.
这是我最喜欢的
This is my favourite part.
我想我们第一个孩子该叫阿秀
You know, I was thinking we should
name our first child Rusty.
你说呢？
What do you think of that name?
我在这里花了不少钱了
至少该让我知道你的名字吧
OK. You know, I spend a lot of money in
here. I should at least know your name.
- Hey.
送你的，今天是你的生日
I brought you this.
I knew it was your birthday.
很漂亮的盆景，看来像块桌布
- Thanks.
- It's a nice plant. Looks like a tablecloth.
我不能多留，我得走了
Look, I can't stay. I gotta go.
我能打电话给你吗？
- Can I call you?
- Do you have my work number?
你有我办公室的电话吗？没有
No.
有没有笔？
Got a pen?
今天你穿蓝色，我也穿蓝色
OK, now, you're wearing blue,
I'm wearing blue.
可不是真有缘吗？
Is this some sort of weird coincidence?
我想恐怕还不止呢！
I don't think so.
I think it's something more.
你住在这里吗？
- Do you live here?
我只是个过客
- No. I'm just passing through.
三点到五点之间别打电话  因为那时候我最忙
Look, don't call between three and five,
cos I get real busy, OK?
- OK.
再见
See ya.
我喜欢她，她是个好女孩
真好
I like her.
She's a very nice girl. Very nice.
我看要下雨了
I think it's gonna rain.
已经下雨了
It is raining.
嗯
Yeah.